https://www.webtogo.de/privacy-policy/

Approval for the processing of personal data
In order to provide its service WebToGo GmbH (“WebToGo”) needs personal information from its customers. We therefore ask you to approve processing of your personal data. You herewith agree that:
1. WebToGo records, stores, processes, uses and transfers your personal data, with particular reference to yourregistration information use of the WebToGo IDA Systems services. In particular date, time, duration of your access and location from which you have accessed the service. Moreover data concerning access to third party websites, if that access was via WebToGo (below summed up as “data”) according to the following articles.
WebToGo records, stores, processes and uses the data for the following purposes:
to generate the WebToGo service, for advertising or conducting market research for WebToGo.
to provide the required electronic data processing, improve and enhance its software.
2. The collection and storage of data can take place by the use of cookies. For the provision of WebToGo IDA Systems service cookies might be needed. A cookie is a small data unit that is sent by the server to your browser and is then stored on your hardware (e.g. a PC). Cookies are stored on your device when you register as a new user.
You can access your personal data, stored under your name or username, anytime free of charge. This can be done electronically (online).
This agreement can be revoked at any time without the statement of reasons and with immediate effect from the time of revokement. The revokement can be made by post (addressed to WebToGo GmbH, Rosenheimerstrasse 139, D-81671 München) or by e-mail (info@webtogo.de). In case of revocation WebToGo will delete all data stored under your name or username with the exception of those that are recorded, stored, processed and used according to WebToGo’s general terms and conditions.
Security Statement
When you access WebToGo’s sites using any modern browser such as Firefox 1.0, Opera 7.0, Netscape Navigator 6.0 or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.5 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects your information using both server authentication and data encryption, ensuring that your data is safe, secure, and available only to registered Users in your organization. Your data will be completely inaccessible to your competitors.
WebToGo provides each User in your organization with a unique user name and password that must be entered each time a User logs on. WebToGo issues a session “cookie” only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. By matter of choice the session “cookie” does include the username and password of the user. WebToGo does not use “cookies” to store other confidential user and session information, but instead implements more advanced security methods based on dynamic data and encoded session IDs.
In addition, WebToGo is hosted in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders.
If any parts of the English Approval for the processing of personal data are unclear or invalid, the German version applies.
Declaration of Consent
By logging in I consent to the recording, storing, processing and transfer of personal data according to the above terms.
